[
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Tucked at the base of a cliff near the University of British Coloumbia and reachable only by steep hiking trails, Wreck Beach is famous for what?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Hosting college parties every spring",
			"1": "The number of Indian artifacts found there",
			"2": "The numerous ships that have wrecked along its shore",
			"3": "being the city’s only clothing-optional beach"
			},
		"answer": "3"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "How high is Vancouver’s famous Capilano Suspension Bridge?",
		"option":{
			"0": "110 feet (34 meters)",
			"1": "230 feet (70 meters)",
			"2": "260 feet (79 meters)",
			"3": "310 feet (94 meters)"
			},
		"answer": "1"
	},

	{
		"type": "check",
		"question": "Which attractions are in vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Dr. Sun Yat-Sen Classical Chinese Garden",
			"1": ".Kitsilano Beach",
			"2": "Jericho Beach",
			"3": "Knott's Berry Farm"			
			},
		"answer": "0,1,2"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "How large is the Stanley Park?",
		"option":{
			"0": "100 acres",
			"1": "1000 acres",
			"2": "10000 acres",
			"3": "100000 acres"
			},
		"answer": "2"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": " Which Vancouver museum offers an exhibit of totem poles?",
		"option":{
			"0": " The Museum of Anthropology",
			"1": "The Vancouver East Cultural Center",
			"2": "The Botanical Gardens",
			"3": "Vancouver Art Gallery"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},

	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "vancouver outlook located in _______ ",
		"answer": "Harbour Center"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": " What park is here in vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "New York",
			"1": "Toronto",
			"2": "San Franciso",
			"3": "Los Angeles"
			},
		"answer": "2"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": " What is Vancouver tallest building?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Harbour Centre",
			"1": "Living Shangri-la",
			"2": "Sheraton One Wall centre",
			"3": "Shaw Tower"
			},
		"answer": "1"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Vancouver has various exotic flowers such as the magnolias, azaleas, and?",
		"option":{
			"0": "billbergias",
			"1": "rhododendrons",
			"2": "villavallelongas",
			"3": "parma violets"
			},
		"answer": "1"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": " What does the vancouver aquarium rank at the world?",
		"option":{
			"0": "15",
			"1": "10",
			"2": "5",
			"3": "20"
			},
		"answer": "3"
	},

	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "_______ is renowned for its scenery and has one of the largest urban parks in North America.",
		"answer": "Stanley Park"
	},


	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "_______ is the short name of vancouver international airport.",
		"answer": "YVR"
	}

]